I live I live I live alone everyone I'm
you know I got my own little condo it's
a good look I didn't always live alone
they just have a roommate I saved up it
was fine
my roommate was cool but when people
live together they're never equally
clean this is a fact so Rhonda was who's
the clean one top you've hit a clean one
tonight
yes clean one's very proud you see that
as a proud people he was like yes I'm
clean yeah
any clean wood always looks at the dirty
one to make sure they're not clapping no
it's not your turn I didn't say I won't
say dirty but clap if you are a little
untidy maybe you're busy you got stuff
going on yeah yeah these are my people
hey you got a clap as soon as I said it
the clean one went like this so you got
a these are my people and I'm sure you
like me I'm not filthy
not filthy just my old roommate he was
he was obsessive he didn't live life you
know he he stalked dirt
dirt had a restraining order against him
yeah he was always lurking in the
shadows waiting to clean I think I'm
eating a sandwich
I run get the phone I come back the
plate he's gone
it's in the dish rack and and he's not
even home
yeah ss he was passive-aggressive used
to make little notes and leave them all
over the place you know my god forbid I
don't wipe off the sink that will get a
note yeah like attention sink users it
was just me and him so I'm like why are
you it's just me say I'm Dwayne same
mother but you know if you clap second
when you live with a clean person you
know it's kind of cool it's annoying but
it's cool right because you live with a
clean person you never have to clean
because clean P what you have to do it
yeah it's it's a compulsion you can't
you can't I'll fill us right
because our threshold for filth is so
much higher than yours and clean people
we love it when you act like you're not
gonna clean it it's cute it really is
it's cute he's my roommate we try to get
tough right you're like hey buddy hey
hey hey yeah yeah yeah hey you know
those dishes in a sink well you know
they're yours yeah yeah I know I know
those my dishes just leave them there
I'll get home it's leave them
[Laughter]
okay okay okay hey any idea when anyway
now I'm not sure when actually I'm about
to watch the Lord of the Rings trilogy
and then if I read the Old Testament so
I'm not sure
hey guys are great I'm doing
[Applause]
you